<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writingdds on Fiona Paine</title>
    <link>/writingdd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writingdds on Fiona Paine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/writingdd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Debate</title>
      <link>/writingdd/art-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writingdd/art-debate/</guid>
      <description>Someone told me the other day that I’m not good at arguing. Upon reflection, I was forced to agree. So in the spirit of self-improvement I decided to write a series of pieces practicing the art of persuasion. Alas, like my New Year’s resolution to “workout more” this exercise was never started. The problem was that I first needed to answer the root question: why do I want to be good at arguing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethics in Economics</title>
      <link>/writingdd/ethics-econ/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writingdd/ethics-econ/</guid>
      <description>The American Economics Association needs a code of ethics and conduct. If economists want their work treated with the same respect and consideration as engineering, science, or medicine they must create and achieve certain standards.
There is a joke that goes if you get 3 economists in a room you will get 5 opinions. This criticism, while fair, isn’t actually unique to economics. In engineering, there are multiple solutions to the same problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Demo</title>
      <link>/writingdd/theme-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writingdd/theme-demo/</guid>
      <description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
 Block quotes are written like so.
They can span multiple paragraphs, if you like.
 Some text, and some code and then a nice plain link with title.
and then
 Create a list by starting a line with +, -, or * Sub-lists are made by indenting 2 spaces:  Marker character change forces new list start: Ac tristique libero volutpat at  Very easy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>